smumn.edu 2019-04-02

# Privacy Policy | Saint Mary's University of Minnesota

## Online Privacy Policy

Committed to respecting your privacy

Saint Mary’s University of Minnesota is committed to respecting your privacy as you use our external website: www.smumn.edu. We collect no information about you, other than information automatically collected and stored when you visit our website, unless you choose to provide information to us.

**Information Automatically Collected:**  
When you visit our website, we automatically collect and temporarily store the following information about your visit: the date and time of your visit; the pages you visited; and the domain and IP address and software (browser and platform) by which you accessed our website. This information does not identify your name, username, email address, or other personal information. We collect and review this information in order to evaluate the effectiveness of our web presence and to improve the experience of visitors to our website.

Our websites are not used to track, collect, or distribute personal information unless it is submitted voluntarily in an application or form. Our site logs do generate usage data such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but all shared information is devoid of personal information and cannot be used to construct such information.

**Information Personally Provided:**  
We do not require you to provide personal information to visit our website; however, you may choose to provide us with personal information through an e-mail message, form, survey, etc. This information is used only to fulfill the stated purpose of your communication and/or participation.

**Disclosure:**  
We will not disclose, give, sell, or transfer any personal information about our online visitors to third parties except as required by law.

**Links:**  
Our website has links to other non-profit, educational, and governmental institutions, and in a few cases, private organizations. You are subject to those sites’ privacy policies when you leave this site. Reference in this website to any specific service, company, or organization does not constitute its endorsement or recommendation by Saint Mary’s University of Minnesota. Saint Mary’s University of Minnesota is not responsible for the contents of any “off-site” Web page referenced from this server.

**Security:**  
When you submit information on our website, we strive to protect that information. We also strive to protect your information off-line. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secured environment.

**Notification of Changes:**  
Because of the limited manner in which we collect and use information, access to the site constitutes agreement to our privacy policy, which may be changed from time to time without notice.

**Contact Information:**  
If you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the site, or dealings with this website, contact saintmarys@smumn.edu.
